[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
We're going to the Apple store
to make fun of the Genius Bar.
You wanna come?
(Sheldon:)Oh, I always enjoy that,
but I'm a little busy.
(Leonard:)What are you doing?
(Sheldon:)I'm simplifying the task of packing
for our trip.
(Sheldon:)See, by attaching RFID tags
to my clothing...
(Sheldon:)...it will enable my laptop to read
and identify the items with this wand.
(Sheldon:)Then cross-reference them against
destination, anticipated activity spectrum...
(Sheldon:)...weather conditions,
duration of trip, etc.
(Leonard:)Well, that does sound much simpler.
How long is this gonna take?
(Sheldon:)Assuming I can keep up this pace,
three hours 11 minutes.
(Sheldon:)Plus however long it takes to conclude
this fairly pointless conversation.
(Leonard:)Wow.
(Leonard:)Teasing the guys at the Apple store
seems a little redundant now.
- I don't follow.
- I wouldn't expect you to. I'll see you later.
[SCANNER BEEPS]
(Sheldon:)Socks, one pair, cotton, argyle, blue.